const generateQbList = [
  {
    id: 587,
    setter_id: 4,
    question: 'Why is gold used in the Gold-leaf electroscope?',
    A: 'Gold is easily available in nature',
    B: 'Gold is malleable',
    C: 'Gold is conducting in nature',
    D: 'Gold is cheap',
    answer: 'B',
    difficulty_score: 1.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'Though gold is a costly metal it is used in electroscope because of the property malleability. This means very thin and light sheets can be formed from gold simply by hammering or rolling and hence the deflection of the light gold plates increases.',
  },
  {
    id: 588,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'What happens to the plates of the apparatus if we measure alternating charge using a Gold-leaf oscilloscope?',
    A: 'It doesn’t diverge at all',
    B: 'It diverges momentarily',
    C: 'The plates give a proper divergence',
    D: 'The degree of divergence increases and decreases repeatedly',
    answer: 'C',
    difficulty_score: 2.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'The divergence of the plates of the Gold-leaf oscilloscope depends only on the presence of a charge not on the quality of charge i.e. positive or negative. So if the charge changes from positive to negative and vice versa the degree of divergence of the plates remains the same.',
  },
  {
    id: 589,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Dr Gilbert tried to hold a brass rod by hand and induce static electricity in it by friction Why did he fail?',
    A: 'Static electricity is induced only on insulators while brass is conducting',
    B: 'The induced static charge flew through his hand and body to the ground',
    C: 'The static charge was not produced at all',
    D: 'It is not possible to induce static electricity by friction',
    answer: 'B',
    difficulty_score: 3.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'The human body is a good conductor and hence the charge produced by friction flew through his body to the ground. We can tackle the problem simply by holding the brass rod with the help of some insulated holder.',
  },
  {
    id: 590,
    setter_id: 4,
    question: 'Gold-leaf electroscope can be used _______',
    A: 'Only to detect the presence of charge',
    B: 'To detect the presence of charge as well as its nature (positive or negative',
    C: 'To measure the surface charge density',
    D: 'To measure current',
    answer: 'B',
    difficulty_score: 4.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'If the apparatus is initially in contact with some positively charged body and then comes in contact with another charged body and if the divergence increases we can deduce that the second body is also positively charged. If the divergence decreases then the second body must be negatively charged.',
  },
  {
    id: 591,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Two equally charged spheres attract each other Now if they touch each other then they will _____',
    A: 'Attract each other with the same amount of force',
    B: 'Repel each other',
    C: 'Attract each other with less amount of force',
    D: 'Don’t attract or repel',
    answer: 'D',
    difficulty_score: 5.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'The two spheres are oppositely charged by the same amount. So if they come in contact both of their charges are neutralized. So they become uncharged and don’t attract or repel each other.',
  },
  {
    id: 620,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Two point charges of the same polarities are hung with the help of two threads and kept close The angle between the threads will be _________ if the system is taken to space',
    A: '180 degree',
    B: '90 degree',
    C: '45 degree',
    D: '60 degree',
    answer: 'A',
    difficulty_score: 34.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'There is gravitational field on earth so if we hang the two same charges there will be an interaction of vertical gravitational field and horizontal electric field. The system will achieve equilibrium by creating a certain angle between the threads and hence the vertical and horizontal components of forces will balance. But in space there is no gravity. So the charges will be at 180-degree separation.',
  },
  {
    id: 591,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Two equally charged spheres attract each other Now if they touch each other then they will _____',
    A: 'Attract each other with the same amount of force',
    B: 'Repel each other',
    C: 'Attract each other with less amount of force',
    D: 'Don’t attract or repel',
    answer: 'D',
    difficulty_score: 5.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'The two spheres are oppositely charged by the same amount. So if they come in contact both of their charges are neutralized. So they become uncharged and don’t attract or repel each other.',
  },
  {
    id: 620,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Two point charges of the same polarities are hung with the help of two threads and kept close The angle between the threads will be _________ if the system is taken to space',
    A: '180 degree',
    B: '90 degree',
    C: '45 degree',
    D: '60 degree',
    answer: 'A',
    difficulty_score: 34.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'There is gravitational field on earth so if we hang the two same charges there will be an interaction of vertical gravitational field and horizontal electric field. The system will achieve equilibrium by creating a certain angle between the threads and hence the vertical and horizontal components of forces will balance. But in space there is no gravity. So the charges will be at 180-degree separation.',
  },
  {
    id: 591,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Two equally charged spheres attract each other Now if they touch each other then they will _____',
    A: 'Attract each other with the same amount of force',
    B: 'Repel each other',
    C: 'Attract each other with less amount of force',
    D: 'Don’t attract or repel',
    answer: 'D',
    difficulty_score: 5.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'The two spheres are oppositely charged by the same amount. So if they come in contact both of their charges are neutralized. So they become uncharged and don’t attract or repel each other.',
  },
  {
    id: 620,
    setter_id: 4,
    question:
      'Two point charges of the same polarities are hung with the help of two threads and kept close The angle between the threads will be _________ if the system is taken to space',
    A: '180 degree',
    B: '90 degree',
    C: '45 degree',
    D: '60 degree',
    answer: 'A',
    difficulty_score: 34.0,
    acceptance_score: 75.0,
    is_accepted: true,
    usage_score: 0,
    reviews: 3,
    status: 'ACCEPTED',
    explanation:
      'There is gravitational field on earth so if we hang the two same charges there will be an interaction of vertical gravitational field and horizontal electric field. The system will achieve equilibrium by creating a certain angle between the threads and hence the vertical and horizontal components of forces will balance. But in space there is no gravity. So the charges will be at 180-degree separation.',
  },
];

export default generateQbList;
